jackmyers.com 2015-10-29

# Privacy Policy - Jack Myers

for JackMyers.com

JackMyers.com ("JackMyers") is strongly committed to protecting the privacy of our customers. The purpose of this JackMyers privacy policy is to inform you, as a welcome visitor, what kinds of information we may gather about you when you visit JackMyers, how we may use that information, whether we disclose it to anyone, and the choices you have regarding our use of, and your ability to correct, the information. This privacy policy applies to the JackMyers site. Please note that this policy applies only to JackMyers, and not to other companies' or organizations' Web sites to which we link. Our policy will be continuously assessed against new technologies, business practices and our customers' changing needs. All changes to our privacy policy will be posted here so that you are aware of our current practices.

_**Information**_

JackMyers collects personal information when you register with JackMyers and use our products or services. When you register we ask for information such as your name, contact information, email address, gender, zip code, occupation, industry, and personal interests. Once you register with JackMyers and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us. JackMyers automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address, JackMyers cookie information, and the page(s) you request. All requested information on the JackMyers site is not required. You may choose to post additional information about yourself. Please do not post sensitive data on registration pages such as credit card numbers, social security numbers or other personal data. JackMyers is not responsible for your disclosure of personal information on our registration form, sound offs, blogs, postings or other product offerings. You have the option to change your posted data at any time.

_**Disclosure**_

We do not use or disclose information about your individual visits to JackMyers or information that you may give us, such as your name, address, email address or telephone number, to any outside companies. JackMyers may share such information in response to legal process, such as a court order or subpoena, or in special cases such as a physical threat to you or others. And we may share with our Web site partners and prospective customers aggregated statistical "ratings" information about the use of JackMyers.

_**Protection of Data**_

We have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and help prevent unauthorized access, maintain data security, and correctly use the information we collect online.

_**How to Contact Us**_

We have established procedures to ensure that every reasonable effort is made to address your concerns. If you have any questions or comments concerning this policy, please contact [maryann@jackmyers.com](mailto:maryann@jackmyers.com) or write to us: JackMyers.com, Attn: Legal Department, PO Box 27740, Las Vegas, NV 89126.

##  Commentary Archives

September 2015  
August 2015  
July 2015  
June 2015  
May 2015  
April 2015  
March 2015  
February 2015  
January 2015  
December 2014  
November 2014  
October 2014

### See all Archived Material

## MediaVillage.com[](http://feeds.feedburner.com/MediavillageBloggerFeedForMediabizbloggersChannels?format=xml)

[Q&A: The Weather Company on Using Automation to Capture Adspend](https://www.mediavillage.com/article/qa-the-weather-company-on-using-automation-to-capture-adspend/)  
In the first of a three-part series, Jay Sears, Senior Vice President Marketplace Development of Rubicon Project discusses how to use automation to capture advertising spend from small and medium-sized businesses with Ryan Davis of The Weather Company. The two executives appeared at a program titled “$50B Left Behind: Capturing SMB Spend” during Advertising Week New York.

It has been said that the US and Great Britain are two countries separated by a common language. Despite many similarities, we still misinterpret meaning and context between us while using words derived from the same source. For example if a Brit is in “rude health” it means he or she is in “very good health,” which is not apparent to us American upstarts.

So here's my take on ad blocking. Isn't it awful that ads for "Truth," the new movie about Dan Rather and his 2004 report about George W. Bush, were blocked by CBS, which refused to run them even though other networks did?

Any doubts about the continued power of AMC’s “The Walking Dead” or its status as the most popular program on television had to have been eradicated this week in the aftermath of the most shocking television death since that of Will Gardner on CBS’ “The Good Wife.”

The Standard Media Index (SMI) this week reported findings that really caught the attention of almost everyone in media. A service that tracks spending by 80% of all U.S. agencies, SMI reported that newspaper spend was up 18% in September and 16% for the quarter. Their research is directional as it doesn’t include all agencies and does not reflect spends made by clients direct (i.e. Macy’s) or FSI activity handled by specialty placement shops. That said, the numbers are still impressive and are frankly no surprise to us here at the NNN. We saw similar double digit percentage gains for both periods. In fact, for Q4, we are already pacing ahead of these Q3 industry growth figures. With all of the negative press that the newspaper industry has managed through over the years, the obvious question most people are asking when they read the report is: What is driving this growth, and is it sustainable?

[If You Own a Cable Net with "Few" Viewers, You Are in Big Trouble!](https://www.mediavillage.com/article/if-you-own-a-cable-net-with-few-viewers-you-are-in-big-trouble/)  
If you are a subscriber to a Multichannel Video Programming Distributor (MVPD) you’re going to wind up paying more for less … but subscribing to pretty much only what you want to watch if you can afford it all. (And if you are Comcast with all of those cable subs and NBCU, well, just look at both sides of all the equations to come!)

Fourth quarter is always an exciting time in media. Maybe it’s from the old television model, but the season still feels ripe for a premiere. But we’ve seen that model decline, year-over-year, as an abundance of choices and consumer control have fragmented our industry along with our efforts to communicate to consumers. Fragmentation is a funny word to me because everyone sees it as a negative, and I don’t any longer. Perhaps it has something to do with our own premiere this fall, as we welcome a new CEO to Screenvision, but I’m choosing to spend my time embracing the fragmentation knowing that ultimately strong messages on the right platform at the right time will find passionate consumers. We all just have to get better at it.

[TREotM: Monetizing the New Media Mix: Or, That’s Not So Simple](https://www.mediavillage.com/article/treotm-monetizing-the-new-media-mix-r-thats-not-so-simple/)  
Chapter 13, Part 1

Hyperlocal apps connect app users with retailers in a mutually beneficial way. For example, an app can notify you that a Dunkin Donuts is a block away offering free coffee for the next 10 minutes. The user gets free coffee. Dunkin Donuts gets valuable consumer data.

Late winter and spring represent primetime for the majority of companies presenting Upfront/NewFront showcases in New York City. Not so with NCC Media, the advertising sales rep firm handling local and national spot buys for multichannel distributors. NCC prefers to show off its intentions in mid-fall and did so again last Thursday.

Disruption, like a breakout summer hit, is the song playing on every station. At the recent ANA gathering, the Masters of Marketing chorus could be heard singing in three-part harmony: Disruption of media. Disruption of business models. Disruption of agency models. Disruption of the disrupters who disrupted everything in the first place.

Aside from the great company and pizza, one of the best things about our monthly Articles Club meetings is the way in which our discussions often veer from course and we arrive at many a tangent. From an oral history of the Kennedy family to a retelling of respective senior prom nights, we covered a lot of ground this month. Perhaps we should consider publishing a transcript. But for now, I’ve shared below our article selections from the month of October.

One of my main beefs about the online adtech business is how so many people working within it are so narrow in their knowledge and their thinking about advertising. Too many seem to believe that the end point is the technology and the algorithms, and not helping ensure that each ad works as hard as it can.

The TV industry is in the midst of an adjustment period. Between the rise of digital and its impact on TV ad revenue, to streaming and “cord-cutting” alternatives, the industry has faced its fair share of challenges. As networks adjust to the new media landscape, some have embraced data as a lead navigator of this somewhat uncertain terrain. Those that have done so successfully are using this information to not only better understand the landscape, but to generate an intimate comprehension of their audience. Acquiring this knowledge is incredibly powerful and has proved a resourceful tactic as traditional television settles into the digital age.

Click Here for Membership Information
